question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Science & Nature",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Igneous rocks are formed by excessive heat and pressure.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Rabbits are rodents.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Switzerland has four national languages, English being one of them.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In 'Undertale', the main character of the game is Sans.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Cats have whiskers under their legs.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In Heroes of the Storm, the Cursed Hollow map gimmick requires players to kill the undead to curse the enemy team.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "'Santa Claus' is a variety of melon.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "'27 Club' is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Blue Danube was one of the musical pieces featured in Disney's film Fantasia.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "A pasodoble is a 'type' of Italian pasta sauce.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    }
]
